# KARTHIK NR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## CONTACT

(+91) 9344219186 KARTHIK180499@GMAIL.COM WWW.IKARTHIKNR.XYZ

## **PROFILE**

Diligent software engineer with 2 years of experience in application development. Skilled in developing plans, managing projects, and coding. Seeking to pursue masters degree in computer science and software related courses, where I can apply my knowledge and skills for continuous improvement.

# SKILLS

- Python, HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, PHP
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Django, ColdFusion, FLASK, YII Frameworks
- Angular 8.x, React, LAMP
- Google Cloud, IIS
- Full Stack Application Development
- Multi tasking
- Project management
- Team Work

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

PRODAPT | SEP 2020 - PRESENT

- Design UI for appl interacting with customer requirement
- Developing number of APIs interacting with Datasources and getting data as required.
- Server Management and deploying code changes in server.

#### TRAINEE INTERN

PRODAPT | JUL 2020 - AUG 2020

- Worked on the development of a full-stack web application with Angular, Flask, and MySQL.
- Practiced Agile Software Development Methodology, where I was assigned as scrum master, arranged daily calls and weekly status calls.

# **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, COMPUTER SCIENCE

SRI SAIRAM ENGINEERING COLLEGE, ANNA UNIVERSITY | 2016 - 2020 GPA: 7.7

# AWARDS

#### HACKATHON PERI'18

FIRST PLACE AMONG 40 TEAMS SEP 2018

# SRISHTI 2018 - NATIONAL LEVEL TECHNICAL PROJECT EXHIBITION & COMPETITION

TOP 10 TEAM AMONG 100+ TEAMS JAN 2018

#### HACK AND TACKLE 1.0 - SSN COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING

SECOND PLACE AMONG 50+ TEAMS

FEB 2019

#### LEMA LABS, IIT MADRAS RESEARCH PARK

SMART E-MONITOR - LETTER OF APPRECIATION DEC 2017